Mrs. Cooper, we say "Catholics,"
not "rosary rattlers."
(Mrs Cooper:)My goodness, it's a wonder
you people in California can talk at all.
(Penny:)This is like the worst Hollywood
tour ever.
Now, dude, she wanted to see churches.
(Penny:)Hey, they have wine here, don't they?
(Raj(pointing at a crucifixion statue):)Hey, none of our gods
have abs like that.
(Howard:)Yep, that's the last Jew
who did sit-ups.
(Howard:)And look where it got him.
(Mrs Cooper:)Hey, while we're here,
why don't we all do some praying?
Let's put a Iittle church in this church.
(Leonard:)Oh, I'm not sure we should...
(Mrs Cooper:)It's easy. I'll show you how.
(Mrs Cooper:)Lord, Mary Cooper here. Coming to you
from Gomorrah, California.
(Mrs Cooper:)I want to thank you
for the blessing that is my little Shelly.
(Mrs Cooper:)I also want to thank you
for the continued strength...
(Mrs Cooper:)...not to coldcock him with my Bible.